<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: introspection | Shane Niu's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://anklos.github.com/blog/categories/introspection/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anklos.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-10-20T13:11:32+11:00</updated>
  <id>http://anklos.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Shane Niu]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Successful People are successful?]]></title>
    <link href="http://anklos.github.com/blog/2012/03/11/successful-people-are-successful/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-11T10:29:00+11:00</updated>
    <id>http://anklos.github.com/blog/2012/03/11/successful-people-are-successful</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is a Sunday morning. Weather is clear.</p>

<p>I lie on the bed, read one aticle linked from hack news: <a href="http://swombat.com/2012/3/10/successful-people">Successful People are successful</a></p>

<p>This article is trying to say successful people usually have been successful before everybody knows that. Successful people always optimize personal growth for buidling their "success pool".</p>

<p>I cannot agree more.</p>

<p>However, being successful is more than that.<a href="http://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=3688263">One comment on hack news</a> gives a very good point of view. We often ignore that chances play an essential role in everyone's success. If Steve Jobs was born in China, he would not create the great Apple. That's the simple truth.</p>

<p>I believe <strong>LIFE IS A RANDOM GAME</strong>. You may argue that hard working can change the fate. Yes. But hard working should also be seen as an attribute that is set in your body when you are born, and it is random. So a person is created with random attributes, and he will live with random chances happening around him. That's the game of life.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[God wins]]></title>
    <link href="http://anklos.github.com/blog/2012/03/01/god-wins/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-01T00:04:00+11:00</updated>
    <id>http://anklos.github.com/blog/2012/03/01/god-wins</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Assume you will go into two rooms:</p>

<p>Room A: full of latest cool staff like best cars, iphone 5, ipad 3, you name it. Things that contain and represent highest intelligence and creativity of hunman beings.</p>

<p>Room B: A girl, who you would fall in love at first sight.</p>

<p>Which room would give you more inside happiness?</p>

<p>hmmm...</p>

<p>That's why Steve Jobs said his greatest achievement in his life is raise four kids.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
